[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Emilia] I'll make sure
that even the devil himself
won't be able to find
or steal your fortune.
That's Magbanua!
What are Julio's men doing here?
[Lily] Diego, we can't let the Ardientes
take Helena's fortune first.
[Emilia] It's time to give them
my little surprise.
[loud explosion]
[Helena] I want you to be my partner.
You deal with the politics,
while I run the syndicate.
We will be the most powerful
couple in the land.
Papa's men and Colonel Magbanua are here.
They tried to raid us.
-Ouch!
-You bastard!
[Marlon] Lily's with Diego.
They said they would take down
all of Red Dragon's businesses.
They'll try to look
for her hidden wealth too.
Grandma, you shouldn't be angry
with Grandpa.
The one who really wants
to steal your wealth
and your remaining businesses
is none other than Lily Cruz.
[Julio] If she's able to destroy
your brothel and the armory,
the next thing
she'll destroy is your wealth!
[Helena] Lily Cruz can't get that money.
If I lose it all, I'll have nothing left.
Everything will be lost!
No!
[Lily] We've clipped your wings,
Red Dragon.
Now you'll crash right into hell.
[Diego] I think someone's tailing us.
[somber music playing]
Lino.
-Are they home yet?
-Not yet, ma'am.
I hope you're safe, Lily.
[exhales]
-Auntie.
-Anna! Marlon! Come in, quick.
Auntie.
-Ma'am.
-Is Lily home yet?
That's the problem.
I'm worried sick. She's not home yet.
Oh no. Where could they be?
Did something happen to them?
I hope they're safe.
I know. I'm so worried.
[action music playing]
Someone's coming.
-Who's that?
-That's Damian.
[panting]
Damian!
Damian, what happened to you?
-Are you all right?
-Are you okay?
-Hold on, I'll just tend to him.
-I'll help you.
I want to ask for your forgiveness.
Please give me another chance.
Anna, talk to me. I'm going crazy here.
-There's nothing to talk about.
-Anna, wait.
They're not here!
[shushes]
[suspenseful music playing]
Let's go look for them!
Are you okay?
[romantic music playing]
Diego. Diego.
Just a little longer…
and we'll finally be free.
We can finally be together.
Just a little more, I promise.
I can't wait anymore.
I wish it were always like this.
Peaceful and quiet.
Just you and me.
[music fades]
-Mom? Mom!
-Lily!
How are you?
-I'm okay.
-Were you hurt?
We did it!
[uplifting music playing]
Uncle Damian, what happened?
Success, Lily.
All that's left is ash.
From now on, I'll fight
every battle with you.
Thank you.
[voice prompt] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
I can't reach Jepoy.
-Where's Jepoy?
-Custodio?
-Please find Jepoy.
-Yes, sir.
Anna…
We'll find Jepoy.
[suspenseful music playing]
[door opens]
-[glass breaks]
-[screams]
Once a liar, always a liar!
Even now,
you can't keep your promises,
Julio Ardiente!
What are you talking about?!
Didn't I get you out of jail?!
You also promised me Lily Cruz's head.
But look what happened?!
All my money got incinerated!
Well, this would not have happened
if you hadn't entrusted Emilia
with your hidden wealth!
You see,
your daughter is incompetent,
and a nincompoop as well.
Wow! Why are we talking
about me now, Papa?!
Why not? All those booby traps
you set were all defective!
That's the reason why the fire started!
Oh, no! Don't put all the blame on me!
We are a team,
and there's no "I" in "team"!
Win or lose, we're a team! Duh!
Duh! You see? I told you.
She's a nincompoop.
And there's an "I" in "nincompoop"…
-…for your information!
-That's your fault!
-How did it become my fault?!
-Enough. Enough.
Because you didn't raise her right!
-That's enough!
-Just admit that…
-…she took after you!
-My goodness!
-I shouldn't have said yes to you!
-Well, then you would've rotted in jail!
Enough! You're giving me a migraine!
A migraine attack! Enough!
We need to drive them out of this town.
For good. That way, we can
ensure peace and safety
in Poblacion Ardiente.
Do you have a plan?
I do.
But Diego…
I want to hear your opinion too.
Because we might just pull this off
if we really get down to planning it.
[coughs]
[groans]
[grunts]
Hello there, Mr. Madrigal!
I am Natalia, at your service.
Let me go.
Not so fast!
I think you're a bit too weak.
That's why tonight, you are my master,
and I am your slave.
Your wish is my command.
Leave me alone!
Why are you so grumpy?
I already saved your life, yet again.
And I think you should just
be grateful that I'm here…
to take care of you.
-Just rest.
-[groans]
And I hate to break it to you, lover boy,
but I'm all you've got.
I think…
you should just accept the fact
that it's just you and me.
I said…
Let me go.
That's enough. I'll do it.
Where's my stuff?
[groaning]
[groans]
-I already told you…
-I'm fine!
Don't touch me.
[Jepoy groans]
Where are my things?
Where are they?!
Madrigal.
Can you just please
let me take care of you?!
I don't care if you don't
want to fool around. It's okay!
Can you just rest?!
Please!
Let me take care of you.
[soft music playing]
Please?
[Jepoy sighs]
Just… Let's go.
Please!
Please?
[soft music playing]
[groans]
Drink.
Anna. Jepoy called.
He said he was fine.
Where is he?
He didn't say, but he's resting now.
Why won't he just come here as planned?
Doesn't he realize how worried we are?!
Why does he have to be so selfish?
Don't worry, Anna. What's important…
is that he's all right.
So, take it easy.
Me? Worried?
He could never come back, for all I care.
I'm just worried about you
and Auntie Camia.
I don't care what he does.
Lily… I'll try talking to Anna.
Thanks.
[knocks on door]
Come in.
-Governor.
-Yes?
You have to see this.
[tense music playing]
[people clamoring]
That happened in the next town.
Someone made it rain money.
Those poor people!
Do you know who's behind this?
Someone we already suspected.
Ah.
My money! My money!
-[yelps]
-[tablet thumps]
Our people saw Lily Cruz and Diego Torillo
giving your money away to the people.
Governor, what should we do
to Lily Cruz and Diego Torillo?
Shoot them!
No. I want to burn them.
I want to burn them alive!
[Julio shushes]
He's asking me,
so I'm the one who'll answer.
And make the final decision, okay?
Those two lovebirds hit me where it hurt,
so I'm the one
who should make the decision.
And I don't care if your lapdog
will obey me or not.
I can do it for myself!
Wait for me, Mama!
I'll go with her!
So…
-Governor, what's your plan?
-[shushes]
Just get out. Go.
Let me have some peace and quiet.
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
[soft music playing]
Damian, thank you for helping Lily.
You know I'd do anything for you and Lily.
But I hope…
you'll be more careful next time.
-Ouch.
-Oh, sorry. Sorry.
[soft music continues playing]
Lily.
You know how Jepoy and Anna
are more than my friends, right?
They're like my siblings.
But I'm worried about them.
Just when they finally
professed their love
for each other,
that's when they started
hurting each other.
That's how love is.
It can bring happiness.
It can also bring pain.
But, Lily, not all relationships last.
What matters most is that…
they were able to tell
each other how they felt.
It's important…
to let the person you love know
just how much you do…
before it's too late.
That's why…
I will never get tired of telling you
and making you feel
just how much I truly love you.
We don't know what tomorrow might bring,
or the day after that.
Whatever happens tomorrow
or in the days to come,
there's only one thing I'm sure of.
We'll always be together.
[soft music playing]
You must be tired, Damian.
You should get some rest.
I'm not tired.
But I admit I'm getting tired
of seeing you avoiding
these moments between us.
I love you.
[soft music playing]
You love me?
Damian, I am your brother's wife.
You know everything I've been through.
You know--
-You know everything--
-I do!
Yes, I do!
But that doesn't change
the fact that I love you!
Camia, I'm not perfect.
I'm nothing compared to Dante!
I might be a criminal,
but I'm telling the truth!
And don't we all deserve to love
and be loved no matter who we might be?
To be loved for who we are.
I'm Damian, by the way.
-Oh.
Are you all right?
I saw this guy steal your bag.
Camia, I can see it in your eyes.
I know you have feelings for me.
Damian…
When Dante died, it felt like
a part of me died with him.
So, I don't know
if there's anything left in me.
I don't know if I can still love again.
I just don't.
[sad music playing]
All right. I'll go back inside, okay?
Sure, I'll be right in.
[romantic music playing]
Help!
[young Diego sobs]
[young Lily] Hey! Grab my hand!
That's it.
Slowly! Get up! Careful, come on!
My name is Lily.
Mom, Dad, this is Diego.
I'll teach you how to lose
weight even if you eat a lot!
Diego.
Ivy Aguas.
[Diego] I didn't know. I'm sorry.
-How dare you peep at me?!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Sorry?!
-Ouch! Ow!
-Let them go!
-Loring!
You're hurting them!
Let them go!
-Get in!
-Let them go!
[romantic music continues playing]
We've been through so much.
And so many people have tried
to come between us.
And yet, here we are…
stronger than ever.
Our love is going
to last a lifetime, Lily.
There's no turning back.
I love you so much, Diego.
I couldn't have come this far without you.
I can't wait for all this to be over,
so we can finally start
our peaceful lives together
as we've always wanted.
[music fades]
[sad music playing]
[Camia sniffles, exhales]
[Camia weeps]
[sobs]
Auntie?
Auntie, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
I'm fine, Diego.
I just need to calm myself down
from worrying.
But I can't help it
when you, Lily, and the
others go out on these missions.
Auntie, you know we never
go out unprepared.
But something can always go wrong, Diego.
I know how it feels
to lose the love of your life,
and I don't want any of you
to go through that.
I dedicated my life to my husband.
I gave him my heart.
I get that, Auntie.
But you've still got love
in your life, you know.
When I lost Nanny Loring and Uncle Pandoy…
I lost all hope.
I was consumed by anger and fear.
But Lily…
She taught me how love
can help heal the pain we feel.
But first,
we have to be ready to
accept love from other people.
Any moment is the right one…
when we're ready to open our hearts.
[sad music playing]
[soft music playing]
Lily.
Uncle Damian, how's your wound?
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
It was just a scratch.
I've experienced much worse, you know.
Ones that could have killed me.
Thank you for being here for me and Mom.
I--I'll talk to you later,
Auntie. Excuse me.
Diego…
is something bothering you?
Auntie, I'd like to ask you something.
[sighs deeply]
I was planning on… giving this to Lily.
I want us to start building
our life together.
But…
I'll only propose to her
if you give me your blessing.
Diego, of course you have my blessing!
-Yes, I give you my blessing.
-Auntie.
Auntie. Thank you, Auntie.
I've been planning
on asking Lily to marry me.
I was just looking for the right time.
And please don't worry.
I'll never hurt your daughter.
I'll love her.
Anything for Lily.
Anything for my daughter.
And you're right, Diego.
We should open ourselves to love.
Thank you, Auntie.
-Please don't cry.
-Too late.
-Don't cry.
-I couldn't help it!
The ring's beautiful too!
[Damian] You know what, Lily?
I suddenly remembered your father.
He was such a kind man.
He had a heart of gold…
and solid integrity.
Kinda like Superman.
Thank you.
Thank you…
for teaching me how to love again.
Oh, Diego.
-[pensive music playing]
-[no audible dialogue]
So, what now?
Come with me.
What?
-Tomorrow.
-Diego…
Since everything's settled now…
maybe I can finally have
my girlfriend all to myself.
Why? Where are we going?
Are we on a mission?
Are my boyfriend and I… on a mission?
I want to take you out to dinner.
Hmm…
So, my boyfriend wants to go
on a date with me.
Is that it?
You could say that.
Get straight to the point already.
If you don't, I might just say no.
All right, fine I want
to go out on a date…
with my BL.
BL? What's "BL"?
Pick one.
Baby Lily…
or Baby Love?
Diego!
You can't be serious, Diego.
Honestly, that's the worst.
Baby Love's fine.
Baby Love, Baby Love,
I love you, Baby Love…
Or maybe--
I think Baby Lily sounds cuter.
-No, I want Baby Love.
-Okay, Baby Love.
Baby Love. Baby Love.
-Go on.
-Tomorrow, okay?
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Great.
I'll miss you.
-Already?
-Yeah.
[Diego] Tell you what…
Baby Love…
flowers for you.
Straight from my garden too.
You have to make it up to me tomorrow…
-Baby Love.
-Yes.
I'll make it up to you tomorrow.
See you.
Bye. Good night.
Camia, I love you.
You love me too, so what's the problem?!
Too strong.
Camia, I know I remind you of Dante.
Damian, you idiot.
Why would you even mention Dante?
[sighs]
How do I do this…
Camia…
[knocks on door]
Damian?
Damian, I'm ready to love again.
I love you too, Damian.
[romantic music playing]
Watch your step.
You sure you won't come?
It's okay, I have to go.
Agent Salonga's waiting for me.
Be careful.
-I'll see you later.
-All right.
[Lily chuckle]
[ominous music playing]
-Bye.
-Take care.
Sir.
[ominous music playing]
-Arnaldo.
-Diego.
-How are you?
-I'm okay. How about you?
-I'm doing fine.
-Good.
I just wanted to tell you how…
in these past few days, I realized…
how lucky I am because you took me in.
Despite my past,
and despite what my family has done.
So, thank you.
Remember, we're always here for you.
That's nice to know. Thank you.
Well, I gotta go.
I've got something to do.
Are you and Lily going somewhere?
-Somewhere special.
-Special?
By special, do you mean…
you'll propose to her?
[chuckles]
I'll tell you about it tomorrow.
-I have to go.
-Sure thing.
-Take care!
-You too!
[tense music swelling]
Proposal.
[soft music playing]
Damian, what's this for?
I've waited so long for this.
[chuckles softly]
Hmm. Where are you going?
Stay here with me.
Damian, I have to make breakfast.
That's all?
Stop it. Yes, that's all.
[ominous music playing]
[reporter] The leader of the group
responsible for many crimes
in Metro Manila
calls himself the Jaguar.
[Damian] Stealing cars got old real fast.
-I want us to enter smuggling…
-Put your guns down!
-[gunshot]
-[laughs]
[Damian] …kidnapping…
What's this?! What's the meaning of this?!
…and illegal drugs!
Are we going to go against big syndicates?
We'll take them all down.
[laughs]
Jaguar.
It's so nice to see you!
It's your service that I want.
Answer me, Damian!
Are you part of Red Dragon's syndicate?
No.
I can't keep my secret
from Camia any longer.
[ominous music playing]
[tense music playing]
Sorry we didn't get to
help you out sooner, Romulo.
It's all right. I got used to it.
Mama and I have a job for you.
Let's go.
[soft music playing]
This is what I've always dreamed of…
A peaceful life with Camia by my side.
But it'll never really happen
as long as I work for Red Dragon.
Damian.
What are you doing? Come here,
and join me for breakfast.
Wow, that looks good!
Excuse me.
[Damian] It's time for breakfast.
So, what are you waiting for? Have a seat.
Um…
I've got to take care
of something at work later.
-Mm-hm.
-After that, maybe…
we can go out on a date.
What?
If you're not busy, maybe we can…
go out on a date.
Oh, Damian.
You're so silly.
We're not teenagers anymore.
We're too old for dates.
But I'm not trying to be silly.
Camia, I'm serious. Please?
Let's go out on a date.
I've waited decades to ask you out.
I don't want to. Damian.
Psst.
Psst. [chuckles]
Okay. Let's go out.
-Come again?
-Let's go on a date.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Can I taste your apple?
That was my hand!
You'll enjoy this date.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
If you say so.
Look.
Can we forget about
that brouhaha the other night?
Nothing good will come from
fighting and pointing fingers.
Right?
Listen to me, Helena.
Before Lily Cruz came into our lives,
we Ardientes ruled this place
with an iron grip.
Not only because we are rich and powerful,
but because we had one secret.
We had one thing that was
working for us beautifully,
and that is because our family was united,
ready to help one another.
That's why we got everything we wanted.
Of course, we had money and power too.
And we…
we had it all.
Now didn't we, Emilia?
[sighs] Oh, how I miss those days.
Well…
We can relive them again.
That's if you grant my request.
To follow you?
No, Helena!
I will help you crush Lily Cruz.
And in the way you want it to happen.
You're the boss.
We'll have it your way.
Your way will be followed, okay?
We can fulfill your fantasy
about Lily Cruz.
But the only catch is,
we have to help each other.
Oh, come here. Come here.
Oh… Oh!
I love my family! Group hug!
I love you, Mama! I love you, Papa!
Enough, Papa.
-What?
-Just hug.
-Ju--
-Not the kiss part! Ew!
[pensive music swelling]
[suspenseful music]
Tell Madam Red Dragon to start
looking for my replacement.
This isn't the life
I want for my loved ones.
I don't want to be the Jaguar.
[Diego] We don't have
any control over the future.
But we have tonight.
I want to spend the rest
of my life with my best friend.
Will you marry me?
I'm the Jaguar. I worked for Red Dragon.
[Helena] I'm going to take both
of you out of your misery.
Get down!
[gunfire]
[theme music playing]